https://www.burn4free.com/privacy.htm

Last Updated: May 24, 2018
Sakysoft s.r.l. is committed to protecting your privacy all the time. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of what we collect, use and share information when you visit our websites and/or use our products and services.
This Privacy Policy applies to information collected by Sakysoft s.r.l. through the majority of its websites and services, as well as its offline product support services. This policy does not apply to those Sakysoft s.r.l. sites, services and products that do not display or link to this policy, or that have their own privacy statements.
This policy applies to the following products: Burn4Free.
Please read this Privacy Policy so that you know and understand what information we collect and how we use, protect, and share the information.
This policy is in accordance with the European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2016/679, which protects individuals regarding the processing of personal data.
If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us.
Information We Collect and How We Collect
When you visit our websites, use our products, or contact us by email or otherwise, we may collect or ask you to provide the following information in order to help us manage our relationship with you.
Use of Third Party Ad Networks and Social Networks
The majority of the online banner advertisements you see on Sakysoft s.r.l. web pages are displayed by Sakysoft s.r.l.. However, we allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements on Sakysoft s.r.l.web pages. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Some of these ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer or device in order to recognize your computer or device each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you are, or who are using your computer or device, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Sakysoft s.r.l. does not have access to the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks.
If you choose to ‘share’ Sakysoft s.r.l. products with friends through Facebook, Twitter or other social networks, you might be sent cookies from these websites. We don’t control the setting of these cookies, so please check those websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.
Log file Information
Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you make a request to access (i.e., visit) a web page or app.It can also be provided when the content of the web page or app is downloaded to your browser or device.
When you use our Service, our servers automatically record certain log file information, including your web request, InternetProtocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages andURLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. We may also collect similar information from emails sent to our Users which then help us track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Service.
Contact Us
We may collect or ask you to provide necessary information when you reach us by email.
This information may include, without limitation, your name, your email address, your website, your physical address and ZIP code, what features you use in our software, how you use our software, your computer or device information such as hardware and system version, system services, processes, startup items, registry entries, dump files, crash logs, etc. In general, we collect no more information than is required in order to investigate the issue you encounter.
This information is collected to help us to provide services and support, to identify and remove computer or device viruses, and to help us solve the technology problems you are experiencing. By sending the related information to us, you agree to share them with Sakysoft s.r.l.. We will use any such information only when providing individual support or assistance, and will not retain such information any longer than necessary for this purpose. We promise that we will never publish or share any of your personally identifiable information outside Sakysoft s.r.l., nor allow anyone else to use it to contact you for marketing purposes without your consent.
None Personal Information
We may collect some none personal information which aims to validate your registration and to know how you use our software or services. The information may include operating system, device ID, Internet protocol addresses, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages, clickstream data of our websites and our products or services, and the pages or features of our software or services accessed by you and the time spent there.
How We Use the Information We Collect
Sakysoft s.r.l. collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its sites and products. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences.
We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as information on technical service issues, and security announcements.
In addition to some of the specific uses of information we describe in this Privacy Policy, we may use information that we receive to:
Remember information so you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Service
Provide personalized content and information to you and others, which could include online ads or other forms of marketing
Provide, improve, test,and monitor the effectiveness of our Service
Develop and test new products and features
Monitor metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns
Diagnose or fix technology problems
Personal information collected on Sakysoft s.r.l. sites and services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Sakysoft s.r.l. or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using an Sakysoft s.r.l. site or service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Sakysoft s.r.l. abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
How We Protect the Information We Collect
Safeguards for Personal Information.
Sakysoft s.r.l. is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We have implemented a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.
Storage of Your Information
We store the personal information you provide on computer or device systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities.
Technology safeguards
No one can guarantee, and we do not guarantee, that your personal information is completely secure at all times. You are also responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your personal information to protect it against unauthorized access or use. If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer or device with anyone you should always choose to log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.
Controlling "Spam" or Unsolicited E-mail
Sakysoft s.r.l. is concerned about controlling unsolicited commercial email, or "spam". Sakysoft s.r.l. has a strict Anti-Spam Policy prohibiting the use of customer account to send spam. Sakysoft s.r.l. will not sell, lease or rent its email subscriber lists to third parties. While Sakysoft s.r.l. continues to actively review and implement new technology, such as expanded filtering features, there is no currently available technology that will totally prevent the sending and receiving of unsolicited email. Using tools such as the MailWasher and being cautious about the sharing of your email address while online will help reduce the amount of unsolicited email you receive.
Children's Online Privacy
Sakysoft s.r.l. products and services are not intended for and may not be used by children under 18. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 18. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. If we learn that we have collected information of a child under 18, we will delete such information from our files as soon as possible, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law.
Other web sites, services and softwares
Sakysoft s.r.l. are not responsible for the practices employed by any websites, services or softwares linked to or from our Service, including the information or content contained within them. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Service to another websites, services or softwares, our Privacy Policy does not apply to those third-party websites, services or softwares. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party websites, services or softwares, including those that have a link on our website, are subject to that third party's own rules and policies.In addition, you agree that Sakysoft s.r.l. are not responsible and do not have control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your User Content. If you are using a third-party websites, services or softwares and you allow them to access your User Content you do so at your own risk.
How We Share Your Information
Sakysoft s.r.l. does not share or disclose your personal information to any third parties with two exceptions as below:
Third-Party Service Providers
We may hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, hosting websites, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.
Currently the data supervisors charged with processing your personal data are the following:
Hostgator Texas USA - management and maintenance services of some servers - https://support.hostgator.com/articles/pre-sales-policies/general-data-protection-regulation
ironSource, installCore - installation and content distribution platform - http://d1f3drzi4rf2ax.cloudfront.net/pp.html
MyCommerce - ecommerce platform to support software sale - https://www.mycommerce.com/corporate-policy/
4Videosoft - software development company - http://www.4videosoft.com/privacy-policy.html
AVCWare Studio - software development company - http://www.avcware.com/index.html
Leawo Software - software development company - http://www.leawo.com/privacy.html
Tipard Studio - software development company - https://www.tipard.com/privacy.html
AnyMP4 Studio - software development company - https://www.anymp4.com/privacy-policy.html
Xilisoft - software development company - http://www.xilisoft.com/privacy-policy.html
Pavtube - software development company - http://www.pavtube.com/privacy.html
Aimersoft - software development company - https://www.aimersoft.com/other/privacy-policy.html
Government and Law Enforcement
We may access and/or disclose your personal information if we believe such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Sakysoft s.r.l.; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Sakysoft s.r.l. (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Sakysoft s.r.l. services or members of the public.
How to Change or Delete Your Personal Information
If you want us to correct, amend, or delete your personal information, your forum account, newsletter subscriptions, or your support tickets, please contact us with your request. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. However, some information may remain in archived/backup copies to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.
For the information processed by the third party partners, you have the right to access your personal information. If you want to access, correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data on our third party partner's platform, you should contact them directly as they are the data controllers and Sakysoft s.r.l. has no control of those information.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of this statement. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how Sakysoft s.r.l. is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Sakysoft s.r.l. regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or Sakysoft s.r.l.'s treatment of personal information by contacting us through this website. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or believe that Sakysoft s.r.l. has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact us and we will make efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
